<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Samples :: Datasync Community Toolkit</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/index.html</link>
    <description>Samples There are a variety of samples in the samples folder of our repository. You can find a walk-through of the code below.&#xA;Servers A typical server Clients The TodoApp&#xA;The Todo App is a typical data-driven application. We start with data stored in a normal Entity Framework Core DbContext, then modify it to synchronize the data to the remote cloud database.&#xA;AvaloniaUI MAUI Uno Platform WinUI3 WPF</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sample Server</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/server/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/server/index.html</guid>
      <description>A sample datasync server Our sample datasync server provides an “Azure Developer CLI” ready implementation of the TodoItems service required by our TodoApp client samples. It uses Azure SQL as its backend.&#xA;Deploying the sample datasync server Download the sample server from our GitHub repository.&#xA;Sign in to Azure using the Azure Developer CLI:&#xA;azd auth loginThis will open up a browser. If you encounter difficulties, refer to the Azure Developer CLI documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todo App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/todoapp/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Datasync/samples/todoapp/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Todo App is a typical data-driven application that uses the sample server for cloud-based data storage. We start with data stored in a normal Entity Framework Core DbContext, then modify it to synchronize the data to the remote cloud database.&#xA;AvaloniaUI MAUI Uno Platform WinUI3 WPF</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>